A Guide to the Norman Sisisky Papers, 1982-2001
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Norman Sisisky Papers, 1982-2001
The Library of Virginia
40776
46.5 cubic feet (101 boxes)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Rhoda B. Sisisky, Richmond.
Biographical Information
Norman Sisisky was born on 9 June 1927 in Baltimore. His family moved to Richmond, Virginia during the Great Depression. He graduated from John Marshall High School and enlisted in the Navy during World War II, serving through the end of 1946. At the completion of his service in the Navy, Sisisky returned to Richmond, where he enrolled in what today is known as Virginia Commonwealth University. In 1949, he received a B.S. degree in Business Administration. Sisisky married Rhoda Brown on 12 June 1949. Before being elected to Congress in November 1982, Norman Sisisky was a businessman. He transformed a small Pepsi bottling company in Petersburg into a highly successful distributor of soft drinks throughout Southside Virginia. Norman Sisisky was elected to public office for the first time in 1973 as Delegate to Virginia's General Assembly representing Petersburg. He served five consecutive terms in the General Assembly before his election to Congress. In 1982, he was elected to the United States House of Representatives from Virginia's Fourth District. Congressman Sisisky was a member of the House Armed Services Committee, the House Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence, and the House Committee on Small Business. Sisisky was also a member of the "Blue Dog Coalition," and worked to break partisan logjams on issues such as deficit reduction and campaign finance reform. Norman Sisisky died at his home in Petersburg, Virginia on 29 March 2001. He is buried in Temple Beth-El cemetery in Richmond.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1982-2001, of Norman Sisisky (1927-2001), who represented Virginia's Fourth District in the United States House of Representatives. Includes legislative and project files, computer letter texts, press clippings and releases, speeches, campaign files, miscellaneous files, photographs, and special media.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
I. Legislative Files.
II. Project Files.
III. Computer Letter Texts.
IV. Press Clippings.
V. Press Releases.
VI. Speeches.
VII. Campaign Files.
VIII. Miscellaneous Files.
IX. Photographs.
X. Special Media.
Contents List
- Series I. Legislative Files, 1982-2001., Extent: 27 boxes. (Box 1-27)
  The legislative files include information on specific legislation or on general topics. There is correspondence from constituents, colleagues, public interest groups, professional organizations, administration officials, and local governments. Also included are internal memos and notes, drafts, final reports, and studies, copies of bills, publications, clippings, copies of letters co-signed by other legislators, press releases, and copies of testimonies by Sisisky and others before congressional committees. Some of the topics represented are asbestos abatement legislation, the balanced budget amendment and budget reconciliation, appropriations, campaign finance reform, colorectal cancer screening, defense issues relating to Fort Lee, Fort Pickett, the Naval Undersea Warfare Center, defense business, base closure and realignment, issue papers, and military construction, "Fast Track" trade agreement negotiating authority, NAFTA, disaster relief, the impeachment of President Bill Clinton, the Paperwork Reduction Act, the presidential election of 2000, small business legislation, and velvet textile import tariffs. This series also contains awards and endorsements given to Sisisky, co-signed letters and co-sponsorship information, legislative activity guides, profiles, and status information distributed by the House Clerk, and voting record scorecards and publications from various interest groups.
  Alphabetical
  - Academic Achievement for All Act (Straight A's). (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Abortion. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Homeownership and Economic Opportunity Act. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Army Corps Civil Works Budget, FY 2001. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Asbestos. (Box 1, Folder 6-10)
  - Awards. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Baby Parts Trafficking (HRes 350). (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Balanced Budget Amendement. (Box 2, Folder 2-4)
  - Bipartisan Health Care Reform Act of 1994. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Budget Reconciliation, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 6-8)
  - Building Efficient Surface Transportation and Equity Act (BESTEA). (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
  - Campaign Finance Reform. (Box 3, Folder 1-4)
  - Channel Sediment Characterization Study - Appomattox River Federal Navigation Project, 1996. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Class Action Jurisdiction Act. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - City of Chesapeake Cost Sharing - Elizabeth River, 1997. (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
  - Civil Asset Forfeiture Reform Act. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Civil Works Budget Request, FY1995. (Box 3, Folder 10-11)
  - Colon Cancer. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Colorectal Cancer Screening. (Box 4, Folder 2-11)
  - Colorectal Cancer Screening. (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
  - Commerce, Justice, and State Appropriations. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Congressional Human Rights Caucus. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Constituent Contacts. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Contract With America - Tax Relief. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Co-Signed Letters. (Box 5, Folder 8-10)
  - Co-Sponsorships. (Box 5, Folder 11-12)
  - Co-Sponsorships. (Box 6, Folder 1-9)
  - Co-Sponsorships. (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Co-Sponsorships/Co-Signed Letters. (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
  - Co-Sponsorships, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 5-7)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Agriculture, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Budget/Taxes, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Commemoratives, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Environment, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Federal Employees/Veterans, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Foreign Affairs/Defense, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Health/Education, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Housing/Banking, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Judiciary, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Small Business/Regulation, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Trade, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Transportation, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Virginia, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Agriculture, 1994. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Budget/Taxes, 1994. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Commemoratives, 1994. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Environment/Interior/Energy, 1994. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Federal Employees, 1994. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Defense/Foreign Affairs, 1994. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Health/Education, 1994. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Judiciary, 1994. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Small Business, 1994. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Trade, 1994. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Transportation, 1994. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Agriculture, 1997. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Blue Dog Coalition, 1997. (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Budget/Taxes, 1997. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Environment/Interior/Energy, 1997. (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Defense/Foreign Affairs, 1997. (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Health, Education and Welfare, 1997. (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Housing/Banking, 1997. (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Judiciary, 1997. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Labor, 1997. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Small Business, 1997. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Transportation, 1997. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Co-Sponsorships - Virginia, 1997. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Co-Sponsorships - General Government, 1997. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Davis-Bacon Act. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Defense - Defense Business. (Box 9, Folder 8-9)
  - Defense - Fort Lee, Panel on Morale, Welfare, and Recreation, Defense Commissary Agency. (Box 9, Folder 10-12)
  - Defense - Issue Papers. (Box 10, Folder 1-6)
  - Defense - Naval Undersea Warfare Center. (Box 11, Folder 1-6)
  - Defense - Portsmouth Naval Hospital, Military Health Care. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Defense Budget Add-On Requests, 1999-2000. (Box 11a, Folder 1-4)
  - D.C. Appropriations. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - D.C./Labor, HHS, and Education Appropriations. (Box 12, Folder 2-4)
  - Electronic Signatures in Global and National Commerce Act. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Emergency Small Railroads Preservation Act. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Endorsements. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Energy and Water Appropriations, FY1998. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Energy and Water Appropriations, FY1999. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Energy and Water Appropriations, FY2000. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Energy and Water Appropriations, FY2001. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - English Language Fluency. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Fair Access to Indemnity and Reimbursement (FAIR). (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
  - Fast Track. (Box 13, Folder 4-11)
  - Fast Track. (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
  - Financial Disclosure Statement, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Financial Services Modernization. (Box 14, Folder 4-6)
  - Flow Control. (Box 14, Folder 7-10)
  - Genetic Testing. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Guns - Instant Check. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - High Speed Rail HR3700. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Hospital BBA Relief. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Hurricane Bonnie. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Hurricane Fran. (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Impeachment. (Box 15, Folder 1-7)
  - Independent Contractor Tax Simplification Act. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Intermodal Surface Transportation Efficiency Act (ISTEA). (Box 15, Folder 9-10)
  - Interstate Class Action Jurisdiction Act. (Box 15, Folder 11-12)
  - Israel Trip. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jones Act Waiver. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Juvenile Justice Reform Act. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Labor, HHS, and Education Appropriations. (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
  - Legislative Activity Guide, January-April 1988. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Activity Guide, January-June 1988. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Activity Guide, January-June 1998. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Activity Guide, January-October 1998. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Activity Guide, January-June 1999. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Activity Guide, January-November 1999. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Activity Guide, January-May 2000. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Activity Guide, January-December 2000. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Profile, 6 January 1987 - 12 January 1988. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Profile, 5 January - 30 September 1993. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Profile, 7 January 1997 - 30 November 1998. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Status Information, 16-22 June 1989. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Status Information, 23-28 June 1989. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Status Information, 14-19 July 1989. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Status Information, 20-26 July 1989. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Status Information, 27-29 July 1989. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Lethal Drug Abuse. (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
  - Macular Degeneration. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Medicaid. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Medicare. (Box 18, Folder 8-9)
  - Medicare Reimbursement of Oxygen Services. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Microsoft Case. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Minimum Wage. (Box 18, Folder 12-13)
  - Minimum Wage. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Monteiro, Dr. Juan M.. (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
  - NAFTA. (Box 19, Folder 4-9)
  - Nuclear Waste (HR 1020). (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - OSHA Reform. (Box 20, Folder 2-3)
  - Oshkosh Truck Corporation. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Pain Relief Promotion Act. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Paperwork Reduction. (Box 20, Folder 6-10)
  - Paperwork Reduction. (Box 21, Folder 1-5)
  - Pepsi-Cola/AFL-CIO - Petersburg. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Petersburg National Battlefield Park, City Point Unit, Hopewell. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Presidential Election, 2000. (Box 21, Folder 8-11)
  - Puerto Rico. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Quality Health Care Coalition Act. (Box 21, Folder 13-14)
  - Rowland Bill - Health Reform Consensus Act, 1994. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Small Business Legislation. (Box 22, Folder 2-11)
  - Small Business Legislation. (Box 23, Folder 1-6)
  - Small Business Liability Reform. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Social Security Notch Issue. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Student Results Act. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Tax Relief for Disaster Victims (HR 3215), 2000. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Treasury Postal Appropriations. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Treasury Postal Appropriations. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Unborn Victims of Violence Act. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Velvet Textile Imports. (Box 24, Folder 3-7)
  - VA-HUD Appropriations. (Box 24, Folder 8-11)
  - Voting Record Publications. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Voting Record Publications. (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
  - Voting Record, 104th and 105th Congresses. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Voting Scorecards, 1997. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Voting Scorecards, 1998. (Box 25, Folder 5-7)
  - Voting Scorecards, 1999. (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
  - Voting Scorecards, 2000. (Box 26, Folder 3-5)
  - Voting Scorecards, 2001. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Water Resources Development Act - Cost Sharing. (Box 26, Folder 7-8)
  - Welfare Reform. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Workplace Goods Job Growth and Competitiveness Act. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Workplace Preservation Act - Ergonomics. (Box 27, Folder 3-5)
  - Year 2000 Readiness and Responsibility Act (Y2K). (Box 27, Folder 6-7)
- Series II. Project Files, 1982-2001., Extent: 26 boxes. (Box 28-53)
  The project files includes material on the establishment, construction, renovation, or maintenance of projects of local interest in Virginia's Fourth Congressional district. Some of the projects, issues, or groups represented include the dredging of the Appomattox River, Army Corps of Engineers projects and Norfolk District overviews, the Atlantic Intercoastal Waterway Bridge at Great Bridge, the City Point Unit of the Petersburg National Battlefield, Consolidated Launcher Technology, Elizabeth River restoration, defense conversion projects, empowerment zones, cleanup of the Former Nansemond Ordnance Depot, Hampton Roads light rail, the Great Dismal Swamp National Wildlife Refuge, housing projects and issues, Hurricane Floyd relief, the James Madison Memorial Fellowship Foundation and commemorative coin, the Lake Gaston pipeline project, the Petersburg tornado in 1993, Route 168 in Chesapeake and other transportation projects, and wetlands conservation. This series contains notes, clippings, correspondence, interoffice memoranda, background materials on specific projects, drafts, reports, feasibility studies, grant proposals and notifications, news releases, and publications. Copies of Sisisky's newsletter to constituents are also included in this series.
  - Abex Superfund Site - Portsmouth. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Air and Space Museum Extension. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Allied Signal. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Alzheimer's Disease Prevention Initiative. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - American Heritage Rivers. (Box 28, Folder 5-6)
  - AmeriCorp VISTA Funding. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Appomattox River Dredging. (Box 28, Folder 8-10)
  - Army Corps of Engineers. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Army Corps of Engineers, 9 March 2000. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Army Corps of Engineers Budget Request FY1999. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Army Corps of Engineers - Civil Works Budget Request, FY1993. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Army Corps of Engineers - Civil Works Budget Request, FY1997. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Army Corps of Engineers - Civil Works Overview, Norfolk District - 19 April 1995. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Army Corps of Engineers - Jones Creek Final Feasibility Report. (Box 29, Folder 7-8)
  - Army Corps of Engineers - Nansemond River/Chuckatuck Creek Comprehensive Watershed Study - Final Reconnaissance Report. (Box 29, Folder 9-10)
  - Army Corps of Engineers - Norfolk District Overview. (Box 29, Folder 11-12)
  - Army Corps of Engineers - Norfolk District Overview. (Box 30, Folder 1-5)
  - Atlantic Intercoastal Waterway Bridge - Great Bridge. (Box 30, Folder 6-9)
  - Babcock and Wilcox ST Company, Little Rock. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Base Closures - Norfolk. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Battle of Great Bridge. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Bennetts Creek. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Bernard, Alfred - Tax Idea. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Beth Sholom Woods. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Boykins Tavern - Isle of Wight. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Brockwell, John W. - Lead Abatement Grant. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Bulletproof Vest Partnership Program. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Bureau of Justice Assistance Grants. (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Campbell Foundry. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Caroline to Campbell Power Line. (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Census Office, 2000. (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Center for Innovative Technology. (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Central Virginia Council of Chambers. (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Chesapeake Bay Program. (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Chesapeake Bay Restoration. (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Chesapeake Capital Lending Fund - Application to Small Business Administration, 1994. (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Chesapeake Expressway. (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Chesapeake Medical Status. (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Chesterfield/Colonial Heights Drug Court. (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Chesterfield Mobile Office Mailing. (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Children's Center. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Children's Hospital of The King's Daughters. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Children's Hospital of The King's Daughters Grant. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Chincoteague Educational and Administrative Center. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - City Line Road. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - City Point. (Box 32, Folder 6-9)
  - Cleaner Technology Substitute Assessment. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Colonial Williamsburg. (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Colonial Williamsburg - TOP Grant. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Committee for Citizen Awareness Videos. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Community Development Block Grant. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Consolidated Launcher Technology (CLT). (Box 32, Folder 15-17)
  - Consumer Housing Fair. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - COPS in Schools Grant. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Crater District Area Agency on Aging. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Crewe Access Road. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - CSX Noise Problem. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Davis-Bacon Wages/Naval Hospital. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Deep Creek Bridge. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Defense Conversion. (Box 33, Folder 8-9)
  - Diabetes Institute - Telemedicine Project. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Diabetes Research. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Dismal Swamp Canal Trail and Greenway. (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Drug Courts. (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - East Suffolk Gateway. (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - East Washington Street Plan - Suffolk. (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Eastern Virginia Superport. (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Elizabeth River Basin Environmental Restoration, 1997. (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Elizabeth River Cleanup Project. (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Elizabeth River Project. (Box 33, Folder 19-21)
  - Elizabeth River Project. (Box 34, Folder 1-7)
  - Empowerment Zone - Norfolk/Portsmouth. (Box 34, Folder 8-13)
  - Engineering, Inc. Technology Reinvestment Project, 1993. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Solutions, Inc.. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - EPA Payback - Hopewell. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - EPERC - St. Paul's College. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Exeter Site - Hopewell. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Federal Funds for Short-Term Colleges. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - FEMA - Chesapeake Flooding. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Former Nansemond Ordnance Depot. (Box 35, Folder 8-11)
  - Fort Lee Natural Gas Vehicles. (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Franklin Redevelopment and Housing Authority. (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - City of Franklin/Southampton Economic Development Corp.. (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - GEAR UP Program. (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Gender Equity Project. (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Gilmerton Bridge. (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Governor's School. (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
  - Grant Announcements. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Grant Award Notices. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Grants. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Great Bridge Post Office. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Great Dismal Swamp National Wildlife Refuge. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Great Dismal Swamp - Public Use Development Concepts, 2001. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Great Dismal Swamp Public Use Plan. (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Great Dismal Swamp - Savage Tract. (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Great Dismal Swamp - Interior Appropriations. (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Greater Richmond Transit Company. (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Greensville Memorial Hospital. (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Hampton Roads Debris Removal. (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Hampton Roads Light Rail. (Box 36, Folder 15-16)
  - Hampton Roads Light Rail Transit Project. (Box 36, Folder 17-20)
  - Hampton Roads Light Rail Transit Project. (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
  - Hampton Roads Partnership. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Hampton Roads Transit. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Hampton University Aerospace Institute. (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Hampton University Virtual Parts Engineering Research Center. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Hercules Corp. CMC Tariff. (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - HHS Grant Programs. (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Highway Advisory Radio System. (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Hill, Oliver - Presidential Medal of Freedom. (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Housing. (Box 38, Folder 1-4)
  - Housing Conference - Suffolk, 1991. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Housing Equity Fund/FHLMC. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Housing Fair Mailings. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - HUD Grants. (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - HUD - Real Estate Settlement Procedures. (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Hurricane Floyd. (Box 38, Folder 10-13)
  - Hyde Park Farm Project. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - I-64 Widening - Chesapeake. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - I-95/I-295 Designation. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Ice Storms - FEMA. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Ida Barbour Public Housing Project. (Box 39, Folder 5-8)
  - Impact Aid. (Box 39, Folder 9-11)
  - Indian River/Mt. Trashmore. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Ingleside - Amelia County. (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Integrated Criminal Justice Information System. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - ITT Defense and Electronics - Conversions. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Jackson-Feild Homes. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - James Madison Coin. (Box 40, Folder 5-8)
  - James Madison/Coins. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - James Madison Fellowship Program. (Box 40, Folder 10-11)
  - James Madison Memorial Fellowship Foundation. (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Jamestown Ferry Boat Docking Facilities. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Job Corps Centers. (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Job Training Partnership Act - Crater Planning District. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Jones Creek. (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Jordan Bridge. (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Kanawha Canal. (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Life Skills for State and Local Prisoners. (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Lynchburg Education Request. (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Lake Gaston Shoreline Management Plan. (Box 41, Folder 9-10)
  - Louisa Airport. (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Lake Gaston Pipeline. (Box 41, Folder 12-16)
  - Lake Gaston Pipeline. (Box 42, Folder 1-9)
  - Manakin-Sabot Post Office. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Massey Cancer Center. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Motorola. (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - NAACP/Rental Rehabilitation Program - Suffolk. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Nansemond River. (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - NASA/HHS Women's Health Technology Initiative. (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - National Sea Grant College Program. (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - National Shipbuilding Initiative. (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - National Technology Center. (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - National Writing Project. (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - NEA-PAC Questionnaire, 1998. (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Nesbitt, Andriko - Food Stamp Proposal. (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Newsletters, 1987-1995. (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Newsletters, 1997-2000. (Box 43, Folder 14)